foreign
[Music]
next we have best use of AI for customer
experience insurance and the winner is
FWD group and Miss Dr Yao Yu Hui group
chief of data accepting the award
[Applause]
[Music]
as one of the very few uh award
recipients from the insurance industry
is a great honor to received this award
again in the next in the second Years
thank you digital bank and also the
panel judges
he's agreed
gift to celebrate activity 10 years
anniversary
moving forward we will continue to
empower more AI around our customer
journey to change the way people feel
about insurance thank you and also
congratulations to all the winners
tonight thank you foreign